https://bitlessbridle.com/privacy-notice/

USA Toll Free: 877-942-4277 | Contact Us | My Account
Free shipping on orders of $75 or more!
Search for:
Search
Home / Privacy NoticeReturn to Previous Page Privacy Notice
Bitless Bridle, Inc Privacy Policy Information Collection We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We  will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will NOT share your information with any third party outside of our organization,  Your personal information will be used only when  necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. You will not receive advertisments or any other unsolicited email from us. Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Search engine Use this form to find things you need
Search
FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $75.00! Orders will be sent via UPS SurePost. Orders under $75.00 ship at a flat rate of $6.95. New Lower Flat Rate Shipping for International orders $25.00 (Canada $20.00). All orders sent Air Mail 6-10 days for delivery.
Don't show this popup again
